Software Developer

616 Korongo Road Nairobi, 00100 Kenya +254 703 987 323 puritynyaboke@gmail.com https://github.com/purity-nyaboke

http://www.linkedin.com/in/nyaboke-purity-357636233

Personal Statement

An open mind and the capacity to seize opportunities are highly valued by Purity Nyaboke. A goal-oriented approach aids Purity Nyaboke in pursuing a profession in software development. Purity Nyaboke collaborates with her classmates in class to complete various projects because she believes in collaboration and achieving success in all domains, and ideally, she is looking forward to applying the knowledge she has learned to solve problems in the future.

Technical Skills

- Familiarity with basics in Python such as data types and data structure such as List, Set, Tuple, and Dictionaries.
- Knowledge of Kotlin basics such as Data Class and Inheritance.
- Capable of storing data in GitHub and hosting websites in Netlify.
- Knowledge of HTML/CSS and JavaScript to create responsive websites.
- Knowledge of UX Research that enables understanding of usability testing before launching a product.

Education

AkiraChix

codeHive - Diploma in Information Technology

February 2021- November 2021

Relevant Courses:

Frontend-Development -

- How the internet works, computer software and Hardware.
- Values and types, loops, and conditions.

Frontend-Mobile -

 Basic knowledge of data types, Arrays, Lists, and Object-Oriented Programming(OOP) in Kotlin. Capable of creating layouts and recycler views in building mobile apps in Android Studio.

UX Research

- User experience and design thinking.
- User Research and why we do it.

UI/UX Design

- Elements and Principle of Design.
- Ideation, Prototyping, designing Logos, posters, and flyers.
- Use of Figma, Adobe Photoshop, and Adobe Illustrator.

Backend Development

- Basic knowledge of Linux, Arithmetic Operations, and Comparison Operations.
- Able to understand data types, List, Tuple, Dictionaries, and Set.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

IoT Project — Face Detection and Recognition using Raspberry-Pi

UX Research skills, I was able to identify the factors that contribute to the high rate of theft and fraud. I choose to use the Raspberry Pi, Python, and open CV libraries to aid in face detection and identification which shall help to reduce the crime rate.

Fronted-Web — An e-Commerce website using Html & CSS and JavaScript.

I Am currently working on an E-commerce website. The website will help users to buy their products online..

Curriculum Vitae

Nyaboke Purity

Software Developer

543 Ndege Road Nairobi, 00100 Kenya

Age: 21 years Gender: Female

Phone Number: +254 703 987 323

Email: sassynyabox@gmail.com

Zodiac Sign: Gemini

Personal Statement

An open mind, self-driven, humble, hardworking, very good multitasker, can work well under pressure and under minimal supervision. Looking for a job to help the company achieve its goals and shine.

Things I am Good At

Python, Babysitting, MS Office, Githab, HTML/CSS and JavaScrpt, Kotlin

Where I Studied

AkiraChix

codeHive - Diploma in Information Technology

February 2023 - November 2001

I am gaining skills in technology and hoping to use technology to inspire and transform the girls from my community to change the world of technology and prove that what a man can do a woman can do 10X better.

Mirithu Girls High school

2017-2020

Kenya certificate of secondary education

Scored C+

Sunlight Primary School 2009-2016 KCPE

Where I have worked

AIC Kamangu academy

Untrained teacher

June-2021-April 2022

During my work here I taught Mathematics and English. I developed my leadership skills as the scouts teacher.

Greenchey Autosales Limited

Sales representative

Jan 2021 - May 2021

My Project

- Built a website
- Created a to-do list

Interests

Socializing, I have strong skill to socialize with people regarding of their geographic.

Software Developer

+254 703 987 323

puritynyaboke@gmail.com
https://github.com/purity-nyaboke

Personal Statement

An open mind, self-driven, humble, hardworking, very good multitasker, can work well under pressure and under minimal supervision. Looking for a job to help the company achieve its goals and shine.

Things I am Good At

Python, Babysitting, MS Office, Github, HTML/CSS and JavaScript, Kotlin

Where I Studied

AkiraChix - codeHive (February 2023 - Present) Diploma in Information Technology

Mirithu Girls High School

(Feb 2017 - Nov 2020)

Kenya Certificate of Secondary Education

Sunlight Primary School

(Jan 2009 - Nov 2016)

Kenya Certificate of Primary Education

Where I have worked

AIC Kamangu academy

(Jun 2021 - Apr 2022)

Teacher - Mathematics and English

She developed leadership skills and organization skills while managing a class of 40 students.

Greenchey Autosales Limited

(Jan 2021 - May 2021)

Sales Representative

My Projects

- Built a website
- · Created a to-do list

Interests

Interpersonal skills: Enjoy interacting with people from diverse backgrounds while attending networking events.

Software Developer

+254 703 987 323

<u>puritynyaboke@gmail.com</u> https://qithub.com/purity-nyaboke

Personal Statement

An open mind, self-driven, humble, hardworking, very good multitasker, can work well under pressure and under minimal supervision. Looking for a job to help the company achieve its goals and shine.

Skills

Python, Babysitting, MS Office, Github, HTML/CSS and JavaScript, Kotlin

Education

AkiraChix - codeHive

(February 2023 - Present)

Diploma in Information Technology

Mirithu Girls High School

(Feb 2017 - Nov 2020)

Kenya Certificate of Secondary Education

Sunlight Primary School

(Jan 2009 - Nov 2016)

Kenya Certificate of Primary Education

Experience

AIC Kamangu academy

(Jun 2021 - Apr 2022)

Teacher - Mathematics and English

She developed leadership skills and organization skills while managing a class of 40 students.

Greenchey Autosales Limited

(Jan 2021 - May 2021) Sales Representative

Projects

- Built a website
- Created a to-do list

Interests

Interpersonal skills: Enjoy interacting with people from diverse backgrounds while attending networking events.

Software Developer

+254 703 987 323

puritynyaboke@gmail.com https://github.com/purity-nyaboke

Personal Statement

An open mind, self-driven, humble, hardworking, very good multitasker, can work well under pressure and under minimal supervision. Looking for a job to help the company achieve its goals and shine.

Skills

Python, Github, HTML/CSS and JavaScript, Kotlin

Education

AkiraChix - codeHive (February 2023 - Present) Diploma in Information Technology

Projects

- Built a website
- Created a to-do list

References

Steven Njoroge

Co-Founder & Product Designer, Arcade Agency stephen.njoroge@arcade.com

Linda Kamau

Co-Founder & Managing Director, AkiraChix lkamau@akirachix.com

Software Developer

+254 703 987 323

puritynyaboke@gmail.com
https://github.com/purity-nyaboke

Personal Statement

A curious mind and the capacity to seize opportunities are highly valued by Purity. Enjoys working with her classmates to complete various projects because she values collaboration and seeks to hone her interpersonal skills. She is looking forward to collaborating with developers to produce clean code so as to launch quality products.

Skills

- Proficient in developing web applications using HTML/CSS, and JavaScript.
- Capable of storing data in GitHub and hosting websites in Netlify.
- Familiarity with basics in Python such as data types and data structure such as List, Set, Tuple, and Dictionaries.
- Ability to use Kotlin and Android Studio to create Mobile Apps.

Education

AkiraChix - codeHive

(February 2023 - Present)
Diploma in Information Technology

Relevant Courses

Frontend Development

- Exceptions and Modules Handling and maintaining program flow using JavaScript
- DOM Creation, change, and elimination of elements from a document using JavaScript

Mobile Development

- Basic knowledge of data types, Arrays, Lists, and Object-Oriented Programming(OOP) in Kotlin.
- Capable of creating layouts and recycler views in building mobile apps in Android Studio.

Backend Development

- · Basic knowledge of Linux, Arithmetic Operations, and Comparison Operations.
- Able to understand data types, List, Tuple, Dictionaries, and Set.

Projects

Breaking bad API

A React-built website. It consumes a third party API from Breaking Bad documentation(a popular series). Users can filter through all characters of the show. https://breaking-bad-api-reactapp.netlify.app

Shopping List

Created a shopping application using Python that enabled users to add and remove items from their cart.

https://github.com/Shamimgardobuya/Shopping2/blob/main/shopping2.py

References

Steven Njoroge Co-Founder & Product Designer, Arcade Agency stephen.njoroge@arcade.com

Linda Kamau

Co-Founder & Managing Director, AkiraChix lkamau@akirachix.com